hi spring fans in this installment of
嗨， Spring 粉丝在本期中
spring tips we're going to look at
我们将要看的 Spring 提示
spring data Couchbase now some of you
spring data Couchbase现在有些人
may know that I did a done a few talks
可能知道我做了几个演讲
and I did a blog post a few years ago on
几年前我写了一篇博客文章
spring data Couchbase and I did it on in
spring data Couchbase，我在
terms of Couchbase two and three that oh
Couchbase的两个和三个的条件哦
well now spring data Couchbase for Dino
现在，Dino的 spring data Couchbase
is out and with it comes an updated
出来了，随之而来的是更新
spring data Couchbase binding whether
Spring数据是否与Couchbase绑定
the binding itself has been rewritten
绑定本身已被重写
for the ground up to integrate better
为了更好地整合
with the touch base for server so in
与服务器的触摸底座
this in spring tip we're going to take a
在 Spring 的这个技巧中，我们将采取
look at couch base and sort of the
看沙发底座和那种
modern updated API there's not a whole
现代更新的API并不完整
lot to offer here that's new you know
这里提供很多新的东西，你知道
from the programming perspective which
从编程的角度来看
is by design that's very very convenient
是设计得非常方便
but some of you may not know about catch
但是你们当中有些人可能不了解渔获
basin I talked today's is a excellent no
我今天说的盆地很棒
sequel database it's a sort of the
续集数据库，这是一种
mixture Thea the product of the merging
混合物Thea合并的产物
of two different technologies many base
两种不同技术的基础
which is a memcache debased database'
这是一个Memcache降级数据库”
you know caching key value store from
您知道从中缓存键值存储
from years gone past and couch TV which
从过去的岁月和沙发电视
is a document database that was
是以前的文档数据库
originally were written by a stinging
最初是由刺痛写成的
cats I think Damian cats who did among
我认为达​​米安（Damian）的猫
many other things the architecture
其他许多东西
behind IBM IBM Domino right which is a
在IBM IBM Domino权利后面，这是一个
document server from decades ago so a
几十年前的文档服务器
lot of a lot of history there and both
那里有很多历史
technologies had their own sort of
技术有自己的特色
fledgling communities and they
刚起步的社区，他们
eventually sort of merged right so what
最终是某种合并的权利
you have now is a document database that
您现在有一个文档数据库，
retrieves or accesses those documents by
通过以下方式检索或访问这些文档
keys and values and its completely
键和值及其完全
horizontally scalable so you have now a
水平可扩展，因此您现在有了
technology that can scale infinitely
可以无限扩展的技术
horizontally and that you can query very
水平，你可以查询
very convenient and that has a strong
非常方便，而且功能强大
focus on index IDs for retrieval but you
专注于索引ID进行检索，但是您
can also do queries now there's a query
现在也可以查询
language that works very nicely and
语言效果很好，
because of its distribution
因为它的分布
characteristics it makes it a very nice
特点使其非常好
choice for scaling up horizontally if
如果水平，则选择水平放大
the if you need to require so let's go
如果您需要，那就走吧
ahead and build a simple example here
继续并在这里建立一个简单的例子
I'm going to say couch bass demo I'll
我要说的是沙发低音演示
use Lombok here to make short work of
在这里使用Lombok可以简化
the accessories and mutators a lot of
配件和增幅器很多
stuff I'll use
我会用的东西
the touch base starter in spring boot
spring boot 中的touch base启动器
1.4 so of course where it 1.43 was
1.4，当然是1.43
staring down spring boot 1.5 which is
凝视着 spring boot 1.5
due in a minute now but when at 4 was
在一分钟之内到期，但当时是4点
the first first iteration of spring boot
spring boot 的第一次第一次迭代
to include couch based support out of
包括基于沙发的支持
the box that support has been in
支持所在的盒子
development in sort of a branch for a
在某种程度上为
long time it's only now that's baked
很久才烤
into spring grown itself and then I
进入 Spring 成长，然后我
think that'll do I think that's enough
认为那会做我认为就足够了
for us to to get the job done with let's
让我们完成工作，让我们
actually we use the web support and we
实际上，我们使用网络支持，我们
use actuate as well so that way we do
也可以使用驱动器
see the state of our time-space
看到我们时空的状态
connection so I'm gonna go ahead and hit
连接，所以我要继续打
generate here alright and it looks like
在这里生成好，看起来像
we've already got an instance of this
我们已经有一个实例
solve delete that
解决删除那个
I'll hit Darren again open this up and
我会再次打达伦（Darren）
we have couch based running on our local
我们有基于我们本地运行的沙发
machine here so 809 1 there is there's a
机器在这里，所以809 1有一个
console and I'm already logged in candy
控制台，我已经登录了candy
so you cancel and so when you log into
因此您取消了，所以当您登录时
the calculator server for the first time
第一次使用计算器服务器
it'll actually prompt you to set up a
它实际上会提示您设置一个
database and optionally join a cluster
数据库，并可以选择加入集群
if you if you have an existing
如果您已有的话
touch-based cluster running it'll join
运行它的基于触摸的集群将加入
that network if you want but I've
该网络，如果你想，但我已经
already got an instance running a very
已经有一个实例正在运行
small and since my idea but it's an
小，因为我的想法，但这是一个
instance and I've got one node one
实例，我有一个节点
server but the nice thing about using
服务器，但是关于使用的好处
touch base is that the further model the
接触的基础是进一步的模型
subject interaction with that that
主题互动
technology is exactly the same whether
技术是否完全相同
you're doing a distributed system where
你正在做一个分布式系统
you're doing a single node kind of a
你在做一个单节点的
type of thing so I've got a data bucket
东西的类型，所以我有一个数据桶
here the data bucket is sort of like a
这里的数据桶有点像
database inside of a server my kind of
服务器内部的数据库
sequel Demi's it's add a base or a
续集Demi是添加一个基地或一个
schema if you will inside of a single
模式，如果您将在单个
server you can have multiple buckets
服务器可以有多个存储桶
each bucket is also basically it also
每个桶基本上也是
corresponds to a team so you put your
对应一个团队，所以你把你的
documents in this movie bucket right
该电影存储桶中的文档对
right now my bucket is only taking up so
现在我的水桶只占了这么多
much for having so much RAM so I'm not
有这么多的RAM，所以我不是
that for
对于
- mentally I'm assigned I've got a
-在精神上，我被分配了一个
maximum 100 so you know very good
最多100个，所以您知道非常好
operational funding sort of interaction
运营资金的相互作用
with the technology you can garbage
有了你可以垃圾的技术
collect and insert porous unused space
收集并插入未使用的多孔空间
you can delete it and so on
您可以删除它，依此类推
specify any title operational concerns
指定任何标题操作问题
that password for the bucket all that
存储桶的所有密码
test stuff you can specify the width
您可以指定宽度的测试材料
whether gratification should be enabled
是否应启用满足感
and in my case I don't have it but to be
就我而言，我没有，但要成为
useful you need to tell it to
您需要告诉它有用
automatically compact or garbage
自动压缩或垃圾
collecting sort of a new spacer and dead
收集新的间隔物和死者
pointers and so on India and the Davis
印度和戴维斯等的指针
I'm going to cancel because I'm either
我要取消，因为我要么
with the specified defaults and what we
具有指定的默认值以及我们
want to just want to build a simple
只想建立一个简单的
Springwood application that talks to two
与两个人交谈的Springwood应用程序
catchments and so I want to go to our
流域，所以我想去我们的
application up properties I'll say that
应用程序属性我会说
we want to talk to the local host node
我们想和 localhost 节点对话
so the challenge base bootstrapping
所以挑战基础自举
policies and Lucia post is actually a
政策和Lucia帖子实际上是
comma delimited array that's gonna
逗号分隔的数组
that's gonna use to find any no it
那会用来找到任何没有的
doesn't matter we're trying to get into
没关系，我们正在尝试进入
centralized it's not like a meter worker
集中化，它不像电表工人
sort of topology it's just completely
完全是一种拓扑
decentralized so as long as it can find
分散的，只要能找到
any node and then discover the topology
任何节点，然后发现拓扑
for those two the cluster and the case
对于这两个集群和案例
in my case you know is Evernote since
就我而言，您知道是Evernote，因为
I've got one known item so it's a local
我有一个已知的物品，所以它是本地的
host then we need to specify the
主机，那么我们需要指定
password for the bucket which in this
存储桶的密码
case is the movie and of course the the
案例是电影，当然
bucket name itself you have to specify
桶名称本身，您必须指定
which is name so we never should have
这是名字，所以我们永远不应该拥有
done like that and then finally I want
那样做，最后我要
to tell it to Auto index equals true
告诉它自动索引等于true
which means it's gonna create certain
这意味着它将创造出一定的
structures for us on macular connects to
黄斑上对我们的结构连接到
the davyous based on what he discovers
基于他发现的东西
in our application so all those are
在我们的应用程序中，所有这些都是
going to use for the Hat on the box and
将用于盒子上的帽子和
we're gonna go ahead and create a movie
我们将继续制作电影
and ta and I think that will map or map
和ta，我认为这会映射
to the yet it's an underlying document
到目前为止，这是一个基础文档
inside of our cash base bucket so we're
在现金基础存储桶中，所以我们
using the document meditation from
使用来自的文档冥想
spring data or canvases with spring data
Spring 数据或带有Spring 数据的画布
annotation it maps to the spring data
注释它映射到Spring 数据
ORM support and so we're also going to
ORM支持，因此我们还将
specify a key there called ID
在其中指定一个称为ID的密钥
instead say I have an ID you know
而是说我有一个您知道的ID
mapping as well using spring that as
以及使用spring作为
annotation although it now touch the
注释，尽管它现在触摸
cash business itself also sports a
现金业务本身也可以
mapping trimmer inspired a thank you
映射微调启发了谢谢
very much by their experience to open
靠他们的经验来打开
the spring data intubation and we're
Spring 的数据插管，我们
gonna specify any title title so there
要指定任何标题标题，所以在那里
we go there's the title and you know I
我们去那里的标题，你知道我
need to go some Gators and so on so but
需要去一些鳄鱼，等等，但是
sort of doing all that work myself when
当我自己完成所有工作时
he's one buck
他是一美元
I know talk to Peyton all Arts
我知道与佩顿所有艺术领域交谈
constructor and I'll tell his Peter no
建设者，我会告诉他的彼得
one's been sucking out the world hogs
一个人一直在吮吸世界上的猪
instructor okay
老师好吗
and what I want is I need to specify
我要指定的是
both the ID and the title the ID is
ID和标题都是ID
something that we have to specify they
我们必须指定它们的东西
database won't do that for us so we have
数据库不会为我们做到这一点，所以我们有
to provide a value for that as well and
为此也提供价值
we keep that right it's up to the client
我们保留正确的权利，这取决于客户
the producer of the object to create an
创建对象的对象的生产者
ID it's completely arbitrary
ID是完全任意的
we're gonna use a UUID thank you so well
我们将使用一个UUID，谢谢
say class sample movies sale are
说课堂样品电影销售是
implements command and I will open up
执行命令，我将打开
back the component and when I say that
回到组件，当我说那
one inject I'll upon story here so
一个注射，我将在这里讲故事
rejected a funny type but we don't have
拒绝了一个有趣的类型，但我们没有
a repository so I'm gonna do is I'm
一个仓库，所以我要做的是
gonna create a spring data repository
要创建一个spring数据仓库
interface will need repository extends
接口将需要扩展存储库
count base or polyphony so this should
计算基数或复音数，所以这应该
feel very familiar if you've used any of
如果您曾经使用过
the spin data projects in particular
特别是旋转数据项目
with spring boot so movie and then the
与 spring boot ，所以电影，然后
partner key type is of course stream and
合作伙伴密钥类型当然是流
we can define custom queries as well
我们也可以定义自定义查询
alright so let's say I want to find a
好吧，比方说，我想找到一个
record by its by its title right which
通过其标题权利记录
is a very reasonable thing to wanna do
想做的事很合理
we can define declaratively a single
我们可以声明性地定义一个
movie like so so completable future
电影如此美好的未来
movie so I'm gonna say that when D
电影，所以我要说，当D
values is read in synchronous they know
他们知道同步读取值
us notify us of any retrieval of that
我们会将任何检索通知我们
top movie so there's the
顶级电影，所以有
the method we could of course just do a
我们当然可以做的方法
blocking movie but wherever you can if
阻止电影，但是如果可以的话
you take advantage within the
您可以利用
synchronous support pay line so there's
同步支持支付线，因此
that and this gets turned into a query
那，这变成了一个查询
this is using a new anyone to Cuba which
这正在使用一个新的人去古巴
is the query language that debuted in
是首次出现的查询语言
catchments for historically if you
历史上的集水区
wanted to do any kind of interrogation
想做任何形式的询问
or continue to have querying or
或继续进行查询或
economics or predicates on top of the
经济学或谓词之上
Minister you had to use JavaScript views
部长，您必须使用JavaScript视图
so on the server side you go here and
所以在服务器端，您去这里
you go to the bucket in particular you
你特别去斗
can see there's two things documents and
可以看到文档有两件事，
views if I go to the views and I can see
如果我去查看，我可以看到
there's demo reviews which can then get
有演示评论，然后可以获取
promoted to production you so you can
晋升为生产你，所以你可以
try stuff out and environment them and
尝试东西和环境他们和
you know update them here and
你知道在这里更新它们
development thing and then I see the
发展的东西，然后我看到
results here so here's a view for every
结果在这里，所以这是每个视图
single record the database which has a
单记录具有
map function and a reduce function very
地图功能和归约功能
common functional permanent kind of
通用功能永久性的
stuff so we're saying for every record
东西，所以我们说每条记录
that's been streamed from the database
从数据库流式传输的
we're gonna say if we if we see it then
我们要说如果我们看到的话
we should go it's an indefinite matches
我们应该去无限次比赛
a certain query you know this is a field
某个查询，您知道这是一个字段
that we automatically saved for us in
我们自动为我们保存的
the document and the Jason structure
文档和Jason结构
that's stored in database if that field
如果该字段存储在数据库中
the underscore class field equals the
下划线类字段等于
type of our pojo then let's go ahead and
我们的pojo类型，然后我们继续
omit it which is to say add it to the
忽略它就是说将其添加到
result set right so what we want to
结果集正确，所以我们想要
wanna be able to do that but we could of
想要做到这一点，但我们可以
course feel intelligent we might have a
当然感到聪明，我们可能有一个
view that only returns a you know a
查看仅返回一个您知道的视图
movie if this first test is true and you
电影，如果第一次测试是真实的，而你
know doc dot title equals on so you can
知道文档点标题相等，因此您可以
do whatever you want you can create
做你想做的一切
custom views and these are sort of like
自定义视图，这些有点像
stored procedures they get stored on the
它们存储在存储过程中
server itself and historically with
服务器本身，并在历史上
spring data you you could only call
您只能调用的 spring data
these views you can only tell spring
这些观点你只能告诉 Spring
data itself by these method names to
这些方法名称将数据本身
call a view and so here's a spring guide
打电话给大家，这是 Spring 的指南
Couchbase annotation
Couchbase注解
you couldn't tell which document to
你不知道要写哪个文件
which reduce function define a New York
减少功能定义纽约
an aggregate at account for example and
例如，帐户的总和
which of you name to use in this case we
在这种情况下，请使用您的姓名
can let it just use the default or it
可以让它只使用默认值或它
will use and then to queue right so
将使用然后排队正确，所以
that's the query then there's the new
那是查询，然后是新的
query language which looks and feels
查询外观的语言
very much like sequel so that's that's a
非常像续集，那就是
very very powerful way to interacting
非常强大的互动方式
through this database certainly didn't
通过这个数据库肯定没有
have before so we can leave it like that
以前有过，所以我们可以这样离开
you don't need to specify custom view
您无需指定自定义视图
and you can just save some data so we'll
您可以保存一些数据，以便我们
say screen oh I'll say
说屏幕哦，我会说
done well first of all let's delete the
首先，我们删除
data so I'll say this definitely view
数据，所以我肯定会说这个观点
repository that delete all I'll say etc
删除我会说的所有内容的仓库等
and we can map over each title I'm gonna
我们可以映射我要的每个标题
save a record here in the database so
将记录保存在数据库中，以便
say this cut me repository at save and
说这在保存时削减了我的存储库，
again here we need to generate a you
再次在这里，我们需要产生一个你
ready to do so do I do that
准备这样做，我这样做
random you ready to string passing in
随机你准备串入
the title and then we'll say this type
标题，然后我们说这种类型
movie repository I find by title and
我按标题找到的电影资料库
we're just gonna take any one of them
我们只是要带他们任何一个
just to confirm that everything worked
只是为了确认一切正常
so we'll take that one title here the
所以我们在这里取一个标题
arms title and confirm that when we run
武器称号并确认我们跑步时
the query we can you don't interactive
我们可以不互动的查询
it so even though we have a smoke we did
所以即使我们抽烟了
wrong as a collection it's still
作为一个集合，它仍然是错误的
completable future talked about it I can
可以谈论的未来
get it forgot it awesome so do a
得到它，忘记它真棒，所以做一个
completely complete with future and then
完全与未来并存
on delivery of that value we say then
在交付该价值时，我们会说
accept them so I'm gonna say it's system
接受他们，所以我要说这是系统
out
出
correct line okay there's this pencil
正确的线好，有这支铅笔
and Dorothea method record set and that
和Dorothea方法记录集，以及
should do it right so there we are
应该做对了，所以我们在那里
there's a mom would eat that's like a
有一个妈妈会吃像
couch base application in 59 lines and I
在59行和
think we should not be able to run it
认为我们不应该能够运行它
you see what happens
你看会发生什么
now count place itself has a lot of
现在算地方本身有很多
redeeming features a lot of things that
兑换功能很多
make it stand out first of all this
首先让它脱颖而出
supports you know arbitrary kind of
支持您知道任意一种
retrieval of data you don't have to just
检索数据，您不必只是
use JavaScript there's this sequel like
使用JavaScript有这样的续集
language that you can use as well it's
您也可以使用的语言
gotten to yo spatial support very much
非常获得空间支持
like like MongoDB and some other I sort
像MongoDB和其他一些我喜欢的
of know sequel differentiated databases
已知续集差异数据库
but it also has other components that
但它还有其他组成部分
are good for I'll find the online
很好，我会在网上找到
synchronization there's insulin but
同步有胰岛素但是
sugar called touch based mobile which is
糖称为基于触摸的手机
ideal for having under embedded
下埋式的理想选择
application and which is designed to
应用程序，旨在
then connect to a server and then
然后连接到服务器，然后
synchronize the data this makes it a
同步数据，使其成为
great fit for any kind of mobile
非常适合任何类型的手机
application right so and that's just one
正确的应用程序，那仅仅是一个
of those things you get for free by
您免费获得的那些东西中
working with touch base let's see what
使用触控底座，让我们看看
we have here we don't want all of them
我们在这里，我们不想所有人
we want it's been a good night
我们希望这是一个美好的夜晚
so it's telling me that it wants me to
所以告诉我它要我
create the view called movie all and so
创建一个名为movie all的视图，依此类推
in order to do that in order to use Jim
为了做到这一点，以便使用吉姆
Savino and you can look at all but for
萨维诺，你可以看看所有
our purposes I just want to demonstrate
我只想展示我们的目的
how nice it is to be able to use this
能够使用它有多好
which is an arbitrary query and this we
这是一个任意查询，这是我们
don't need to provide a view that's a
不需要提供一个
nice big feature and in time space I'm
不错的大功能，在时空上
in the spring data type space binding
在Spring数据类型空间绑定中
well the spring data type space finding
Spring 数据类型空间查找
used to be a third party project which
曾经是第三方项目
maintained silent screen data ecosystem
保持无声屏幕数据生态系统
and now happily it's part of this bring
现在很高兴地这是带来的一部分
down a strain and of course it you joins
减轻压力，当然你也加入了
contributions and leadership from the
的贡献和领导
touch base team but it gets released and
接触基础团队，但被释放，
taint along with the other spring
与其他 Spring 一起污染
projects which i think is a really cool
我认为很酷的项目
change of events right so here we go
改变事件吧，现在我们去
there's our movie Wizard of Oz our
有我们的电影《绿野仙踪》
unique ID worked as we expected and so
唯一ID符合我们的预期，因此
on and that's it when you have an
当你有一个
application that's talking to babysits
与婴儿照看的应用程序
it's up and running of course I may want
我可能想要启动并运行
to inspect its health so you'll recall
检查它的健康状况，以便您回想起
that I added the actuator the-- it's
我添加了执行器-
pretty good actuator which is a
相当不错的执行器
framework that's designed to surface
旨在浮出水面的框架
operational information about the
有关的操作信息
application and I would love to see the
应用程序，我很乐意看到
health of the touch base data store but
触控基础数据存储的运行状况，但是
it's gonna be there flexing that the
它会在那里展示
applications up about it so you get now
有关它的应用程序，所以您现在就可以
you get you know smart intubation or out
您了解智能插管或插管
of the screen ecosystem with with
屏幕生态系统的
cupcakes
纸杯蛋糕
so again very great as you get working
所以当你开始工作时很棒
very easy to start and so with that
非常容易启动，因此
thanks very much for watching and I will
非常感谢您的收看，我会
see you next time
下次见
you
您